niktajavanfar

nikta.javanfar@gmail.com 613.888.8654

online

niktajavanfar.com @niktajavanfar

highlights of qualifications

members on the product vision.

Building and maintaining relationships with high-profile customers and partners, including: Starbucks, Telus, and Bell.

As a product manager, my aim is to bring clarity to any project I work on, and to align all team

Entrusted with the management of a B2B, foot-traffic analytics product consisting of real-time dashboards and historical reports, aimed at increasing consumer engagement.

Retained as one of eight employees upon the acquisition of BOLDstreet Wireless.

Strong statistical and analytical background rooted in a Bachelor's degree in Mathematical Physics.

Demonstrates data-driven decision making throughout product lifecycles: from market research to customer feedback.

Experience with Google Analytics, LaTeX, SQL Server Management Studio, Asana, AtTask, and D3.

computers

Comfortable with OS X, Linux, Windows

thesis

Static Fluid Spheres and independent research in

the Cosmological Constant-involved the field of general relativity

product demo

An example of a real-time dashboard can be found at http://lbr.boldstreet.com /Dashboards/viewer.htm ?dash=r53o8

other

Violinist, Commuting cyclist

education

2008-2012 B.Sc. Honours. Queen's University

Mathematical Physics

work experience

2014-Present **Product Manager** Datavalet Technologies

Responsible for the management and oversight of a growing portfolio of

commercial Wi-Fi and analytics products.

2013-2014 **Product Manager BOLDstreet Wireless**

> Worked closely with customers and partners in order to ensure that a foottraffic analytics product was staying relevant in a rapidly changing industry.

Summer 2011 **Student Researcher** Royal Military College of Canada

> Presented preliminary research on magnetic field detection in stars at the Women in Physics conference held at Perimeter Institute for Theoretical

Physics, Waterloo, ON.

Summer 2010 **Student Researcher** Canadian Institute for Theoretical Astrophysics

> Wrote a computer program to search for objects in the outer solar system using Hubble Space Telescope data—the resulting paper was published in

the Astrophysical Journal.

current volunteer work

2014-Present **Youth Inpatient Volunteer** The Royal Ottawa Mental Health Centre

Provide support for youth patients who are battling mental illness.